{
    "subject": "resource/K._J._Stevens",
    "predicate": "ontology/influencedBy",
    "object": "resource/Flannery_O'Connor",
    "human_readable": "K.J. Stevens was influenced by Flannery O'Connor.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9873918890953064,
            "question": "What type of influence did Flannery O'Connor have on K.J. Stevens?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9342885613441467,
            "question": "Who influenced K.J. Stevens?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8509905934333801,
            "question": "Who was Flannery O'Connor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8415419459342957,
            "question": "Name a writer who influenced K.J. Stevens."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8186703324317932,
            "question": "How might Flannery O'Connor's work have shaped K.J. Stevens' writing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5896145105361938,
            "question": "What is K.J. Stevens known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5388733148574829,
            "question": "Did Flannery O'Connor write in a specific style?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5173411965370178,
            "question": "What genre is Flannery O'Connor known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5041528940200806,
            "question": "Can you name any works by Flannery O'Connor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47544488310813904,
            "question": "What are some common themes found in Flannery O'Connor's work?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=K.J. Stevens was influenced by Flannery O'Connor.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7743_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name any works by Flannery O'Connor?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7743_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is Flannery O'Connor known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7743_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did Flannery O'Connor write in a specific style?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7743_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7743_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7743_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7743_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7743_124.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7743_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7743_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7743_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7743_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7743_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7743_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format answer:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that both Flannery O\u2019Connor and K.J. Stevens were influenced by each other's work, supporting the statement that K.J. Stevens was influenced by Flannery O'Connor."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}